Finding Aid for the Herschel Burke Gilbert Papers PASC-M.0268
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Projects, Series 1.
  - Honey West, Subseries 29.
    - Honey West, 1965 July 30; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 167)
      Tape reel: 763. Log or Cue #18484-18502.
    - Honey West, 1966 January 12; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 170)
      Tape Reel: 905. Log or Cue# 21544-21547.
    - Honey West, 1965 August 20; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 171)
      Tape Reel: 929. Log or Cue# 19165-19186.
    - Honey West, 1966 January 18; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 174)
      Tape reels: 1268. Log or Cue# 21423.
    - Honey West, 1965 September 17; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 207)
      Tape reels: 932 and 933. Log or Cue #s: 19645-19663, 19664-19709, respectively.
    - Honey West, 1965 July 27; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 207)
      Tape reel: 937. Log or Cue #: 18371-18403.
    - Honey West / Big Valley, 1965 June 24; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 197)
    - Honey West and Big Valley, 1965 June 24; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 207)
    - Honey West/Big Valley, 1965 June 24; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 193)
    - Honey West, 1965 September 20; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 148)
      Tape Reel: 739.
  - Iron Butterfly, Subseries 30.
    - Assorted Papers, 1967 (Box 256)
      collaboration agreements with writers, lyricists & composer; casting ideas; script comments; Four Star Television sound recordings; lyrics by Barbara Best and Alene Smith; clippings; press releases; scripts; song indexes; original treatment
    - Script, Recording and Demo Logs, 1968 (Box 265)
    - Sound Recording, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 192)
      Tape reel: 566. Log or Cue#: 407A, 406-407, 425, 436-448, 408-435, 3 track 17A. Opera.
    - Sound Recordings, 1967 May 24 - 26; open reel audio tapes (Box 182)
      Tape reels: 563-565. Log or cue nos. 299-305, 320-335, 379-405, 370-378, 408-435. Three track original. Opera.
  - It's Up to You, Subseries 31.
    - Budget, Cost, Cues (Box 259)
    - Speed Up (episode title), 1951, August 18; 3 pages; 12 x 14 in; autograph pencil short score, annotated in black, red and blue, 12 staves (Box 39)
      Cue no. 2A. Record no. 711. File title: Its up to you.Short score.
  - The Jackie Robinson Story, Subseries 32.
    - Assorted Materials, 1950 (Box 259)
    - Instrumental Breakdown, April 18; 1 pages; 2fl,ob,3cl,bsn,3hn,2tpt,2tbn,tuba,2perc,piano,harp,strings (5,4,3,3,2); 10 x 12.4 in.; printed form with handwritten annotations (Box 40)
      Record no. 1003.
    - Instrumental Breakdown, April 18; 1 pages; 2fl,ob,3cl,bsn,3hn,2tpt,2tbn,tuba,2perc,piano,harp,strings (5,4,3,3,2); 10 x 12.4 in.; printed form with handwritten annotations (Box 41)
    - Instrumental Breakdown, April 18; 1 pages; 2fl,ob,3cl,bsn,3hn,2tpt,2tbn,tuba,2perc,piano,harp,strings (5,4,3,3,2); 10 x 12.4 in.; printed form with handwritten annotations (Box 42)
    - TeleCinema, Inc memo re Music Sync for American Dreamers, Jackie Robinson Story Cue by HB Gilbert (Box 251)
  - Johnny Ringo, Subseries 38.
    Television series (1959-1960). Also known as "The Westerners."
    - Johnny Ringo, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 146)
      Tape Reel: 767. Log or Cue# 2351-2353.
    - Johnny Ringo, 1959 September 13; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 146)
      Tape Reel: 768.
    - Johnny Ringo, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 147)
      Tape Reel: 769.
    - Johnny Ringo, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 183)
      Tape reel: 267. Log or Cue #2304-5-6-7-8.
  - The June Allyson Show, Subseries 39.
    Gilbert wrote the theme music for this television series. Also known as The Dupont Show with June Allyson.
    - License, Affair In Athens (The Dupont Show with June Allyson Series), BNP Publishing & John Paul Music, 1961 January 6 (Box 252)
  - Kid Monk Baroni, Subseries 40.
    Gilbert wrote original music for this film, also known as Young Paul Baroni.
    - Assorted Materials, 1952 (Box 259)
    - Freight Yard (episode title), 1952 February 7; 2 pages; cl,strings (3,3,2,1,1); 9.5 x 11.5 in; autograph pencil short score, red annotations, 12 staves (Box 43)
      Production no. 1700. Cue no. 3A. Record no. 762. File title: Kid Monk Baroni. Short Score.
  - Letter to Loretta, 1960; Subseries 42.
    Television series 1953-1961.
    - Agreement and Contract (Box 281)
      Between: Gilbert/Laurel Music Enterprises
    - Loretta Young, 1960 November 10; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 177)
      Tape reel: 1251.
    - Music Timing Sheets, Music Cue Sheets (Box 281)
  - Loan Shark, Subseries 113.
    - Tentative Music Cues and Timing, 1952 (Box 259)
      Encore Films, Inc.
  - The Long Wait, Subseries 114.
    - Tentative Music Breakdown, 1953 (Box 259)
  - The Magic Face, Subseries 44.
    - Cue Sheets, Financial Papers, Correspondence, 1951 (Box 259)
  - Man Crazy, Subseries 115.
    - Tentative Budget, 1952 (Box 259)
  - The Man Who Stole the Word "Beautiful", Subseries 45.
    - Script and Recording Logs, 1968 (Box 264)
    - The Man Who Stole the Word Beautiful, 1966 September 13; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 208)
      Tape reel: 1130.
    - The Man Who Stole the Word Beautiful, 1966 October 16; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 208)
      Tape reel: 1131.
  - McKeever and the Colonel, Subseries 47.
    - Correspondence re: Rights and Royalties, 1964 August (Box 261)
      Regarding Joseph Mullendore.
    - McKeever and the Colonel, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 190)
      Tape Reel: 1123. Log or Cue# 10220A-10240A.
    - Now Get This (episode title), 1960 December 28; fl,ob,2cl,bsn,3tpt,3tbn,perc,strings; 11 x 17 in; photocopy full score (Box 48)
      Orchestrator: Walter Sheets. Production no. M11 - Pro. 1022. Cue no. 10220. Record no. 876.
    - Swagger Stick Play Off (episode title), 1960 December 30; pic,ob,2cl,bsn,3tpt,3tbn,tuba,2perc,strings; 11 x 17 in; photocopy full score (Box 48)
      Cue no. 10221. Record no. 877.
  - Models, Inc., Subseries 49.
    - Correspondence re: Rights and Royalties, 1958 (Box 261)
      Correspondence re: "BR 14489 Cue"
    - Cue Sheets, Timings, Budget (Box 259)
  - A Moment in the Sun, Subseries 50.
    - Moment in the Sun, 1964 October 26; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 208)
      Tape reels: 1127, 1128, and 1129. Log or Cue #s: 300-3039, 3040-3091, and 3092-3103, respectively.
  - Monster That Challenged the World, The, Subseries 107.
    - Contracts and Agreements (Box 289)
      agreement and correspondence
    - Cue Sheets, 1957 April 18 (Box 248)
      Cue sheets and cover letter.
    - Sheet Music for, "Full of Love" (Box 288)
      music by Heinz Roemheld, lyric by Alan Bergman/Marilyn Keith
    - Sound Recording, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 145)
      Tape Reel: 44.
    - Sound Recording, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 191)
      Tape Reel: 45.
    - United Artists Corp. Correspondence (Box 267)
  - The Moon is Blue, Subseries 51.
    - Blackeye (cue title), 1 pages; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 16 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Cue no. 14611 (8A). Record no. 2215.
    - Button Pops (cue title), 1 pages; 11 x 12 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 12 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Cue no. 14615 (1C). Record no. 2202.
    - Catsup Spot (cue title), 3 pages; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 16 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Cue no. 14613 (6A). Record no. 2211.
    - Ceiling Leak (cue title), 1 pages; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 16 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Cue no. 6D. Record no. 2213.
    - Chloro-foam T.V. Show, 6 pages; 2fl/pic,ob,2cl,basscl,bsn,3hn,tpt,tbn,2perc,piano, strings (5,5,4,4,2); 12 x 19 in.; autograph red, blue and black pencil full score, 27 staves (Box 132)
      Production no. 18900. Cue no. 9A. Record no. 2222.
    - Contract, Cue Sheets, Recording Breakdown, 1953-1954 (Box 259)
    - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 257)
    - Correspondence, 1954-1958 (Box 269)
      From Santly-Joy, Inc. music publishers.
    - Cue Sheets, 1953 April 1 (Box 252)
    - Cynthia's Picture (cue title), 1 pages; 10.5 x 13 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 12 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Cue no. 14616 (2B). Record no. 2205.
    - Dubbing Information (Box 288)
      Bill from Eccles Recordings, Inc. to Holby Productions for Dubbing - Title Song from The Moon Is Blue
    - End Title, 1953 March 29; 3 pages; 2fl/pic,ob,2cl,basscl,bsn,3hn,tpt,tbn,tuba,perc,piano, strings (5,5,4,4,2); 12 x 19 in.; autograph red and black pencil full score, 27 staves (Box 132)
      Production no. 18900. Cue no. 14600 (10B). Record no. 2223.
    - End Title, 1 pages; 10.5 x 13 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 12 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Cue no. 14600 (10B). Record no. 2219.
    - Enter Cynthia (cue title), 1 pages; 10.5 x 13 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 12 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Cue nos. 14607, 14618 (2D). Record no. 2207.
    - Fire Escape (cue title), 2 pages; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 16 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Cue no. 14614 (5A). Record no. 2210.
    - Hat and Bra (cue title), 1 pages; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 16 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Cue no. 14609 (6C). Record no. 2212.
    - In Office (cue title), 2 pages; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 16 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Cue nos. 14605-6 (2AA). Record no. 2204.
    - Kiss and There (cue title), 2 pages; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 16 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Cue no. 14608 (7A). Record no. 2214.
    - Letter to Otto Preminger from Gilbert, 1953 January 30 (Box 288)
      regarding song rejection for The Moon Is Blue
    - Main Title, 1953 March 19-21; 9 pages; 2fl/pic,ob,2cl,basscl,bsn,3hn,tpt,tbn,tuba,perc,piano, strings (5,5,4,4,2); 12 x 19 in.; autograph red and black pencil full score, 27 staves (Box 132)
      Production no. 18900. Cue no. 14599 (1A). Record no. 2220.
    - Maint Title, 3 pages; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 16 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Production no. 14599. Cue no. 14599(1A). Record no. 2200.
    - Meet Slater (cue title), 3 pages; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 16 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Cue no. 14610 (4A). Record no. 2209.
    - No Needle (cue title), 1 pages; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 16 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Cue no. 2A. Record no. 2203.
    - Patty Knocks (cue title), 2 pages; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 16 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Cue no. 10A. Record no. 2218.
    - Patty Returns (cue title), 2 pages; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 16 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Cue no. 9D. Record no. 2217.
    - Pick Up (cue title), 6 pages; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 16 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Cue nos. 14597-8; 14603 (1B). Record no. 2201.
    - Pick Up (cue title), 1953 March 25; 21 pages; 2fl,ob,2cl,basscl,bsn,3hn,tpt,tbn,tuba,2perc,piano, strings (5,5,4,4,2); 12 x 19 in.; manuscript red and black pencil full score, 27 staves (Box 132)
      Production no. 18900. Cue nos. 14597-98 (1B). Record no. 2221.
    - Repenteth (cue title), 1 pages; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 16 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Cue no. 14612 (8B). Record no. 2216.
    - Shopping List (cue title), 2 pages; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 16 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Cue no. 14604 (3B). Record no. 2208.
    - Show Me (cue title), 1 pages; 10.5 x 13 in.; manuscript black ink short score, 12 staves, ozalid (Box 132)
      Cue no. 14617 (2C). Record no. 2206.
    - United Artists Corp. Correspondence, 1956-1967 (Box 270)
  - Mr. District Attorney, Subseries 52.
    - CBS Release (Box 258)
    - Hysterical Woman (cue title), 3 pages; piano conductor; 9.5 x 12.5 in.; short score photocopy, 6-9 staves (Box 122)
      Studio: Columbia Pictures Corp.. Production no. 851. Cue no. 2B. Record no. 2160.
    - Marcia Tries Again (cue title), 4 pages; piano conductor; 9.5 x 12.5 in.; short score, photocopy, 6-9 staves (Box 122)
      Studio: Columbia Pictures Corp.. Production no. 851. Cue no. 6C. Record no. 2164.
    - Steve Phones (cue title), 2 pages; piano conductor; 9.5 x 12.5 in.; short score, photocopy, 6-9 staves (Box 122)
      Studio: Columbia Pictures Corp. Production no. 851. Cue no. 2D. Record no. 2161.
    - Steve Realizes (cue title), 2 pages; piano conductor; 9.5 x 12.5 in.; short score, photocopy, 6-9 staves (Box 122)
      Studio: Columbia Pictures Corp.. Production no. 851. Record no. 851.
    - Steve Realizes (cue title), 4 pages; piano conductor; 9.5 x 12.5 in.; short score, photocopy, 6-9 staves (Box 122)
      Studio: Columbia Pictures Corp.. Production no. 851. Cue no. 6A. Record no. 2163.
    - Steve's Return (cue title), 4 pages; piano conductor; 9.75 x 13.5 in.; short score, photocopy, 6-9 staves (Box 122)
      Studio: Columbia Pictures Corp.. Production no. 851. Cue no. 4A. Record no. 2162.
  - The Naked Dawn, Subseries 55.
    - Agreements, cue sheets, correspondence, printed/published score "I Love A Stranger" (Box 259)
    - Cue Sheets, 1954 (Box 252)
    - Sheet Music for "I Love a Stranger" (Box 288)
      lyric by Edward Heyman, music by Herschel Gilbert
  - The Naked Hills, Subseries 56.
    - Contract for the song, "The Four Seasons", 1956 (Box 258)
    - The Four Seasons, 1955 December 1; 2 pages; 10.5 x 12.75 in; autograph short score (Box 21)
      Cue no. 14376. Record no. 645. Autograph pencil short score, red and black annotations, 12 staves. File title: Fourseasons short score.
  - Neuteronomy, Subseries 126.
    - Script, 1970 October (Box 256)
      By R. Manus.
  - Nightmare, Subseries 58.
    - [no title], 3 pages; alto,tenor,bary,tpt,piano,bass,perc; 15.5 x 18 in; manuscript pencil full score (Box 52)
      Instrumental version.
      On item: U.S.Naval School of Music, Washington 25, D.C.
    - Agreements, Cue Sheets, Correspondence, 1961 (Box 259)
    - Lonesome Sound (cue title), 8 pages; alto,tenor,bary,vocal,tpt,piano,perc; 15.5 x 18.25 in; manuscript pencil full score (Box 52)
      On item: U.S.Naval School of Music, Washington 25, D.C. Record no. 943.
  - No Place to Hide, Subseries 59.
    - Contract, Cue Sheets, Correspondence, 1955-1958 (Box 260)
    - Cue Sheets, 1956 (Box 252)
  - No Time for Flowers, Subseries 60.
    - Actress (cue title), 1951 September 21; 2 pages; 12 x 14 in.; autograph pencil short score, red annotations, 12 staves (Box 56)
      Production no. 10700. Cue no. 14244. Record no. 1011.
    - Agreements, Cue Sheets, Correspondence, 1951 (Box 259)
    - Barroom Piano (cue title), 1951 September 20; 2 pages; 9.5 x 12.5 in.; autograph pencil sketch, red annotations, 10 staves (Box 56)
      Production no. 10700. Record no. 1004.
    - Bubble Trouble (cue title), 5 pages; 12 x 14 in.; autograph pencil short score, red annotations, 12 staves (Box 56)
      Production no. 10700. Cue no. 14250. Record no. 1013.
    - Customs (cue title), 2 pages; 12 x 14 in.; autograph pencil short score, red annotations, 12 staves (Box 56)
      Production no. 10700. Cue no. 14243. Record no. 14243.
    - Czech Dance, flute,violin,cello; 9.5 x 12.5;11 x 13.5 in.; manuscript ink orchestral parts with parts jacket;ozalids (Box 56)
      Production no. 10700. Record no. 1006. Outside of jacket says: 1perc,2vlns,1vc,1bs.
    - Czech Dance, 3 pages; 2viol,vibra,cello,bass; 12 x 14 in.; autograph pencil short score, red and blue annotations, 12 staves (Box 56)
      Production no. 10700. Cue no. 14268. Record no. 1022.
    - End Cast, 3 pages; 12 x 14 in.; autograph pencil short score, red and blue annotations, 12 staves (Box 56)
      Production no. 10700. Cue no. 14238. Record no. 1008.
    - Four Regimes (cue title), 8 pages; 2fl,ob,2cl,bsn,3hn,2tpt,2tbn,tuba,2perc,harp,piano,strings; 12 x 14 in.; autograph pencil short score, red and blue annotations, 12 staves (Box 56)
      Production no. 10700. Cue no. 14239. Record no. 1009.
    - Good-Night Dance (cue title), 1 pages; 2viol,vibra,cello,bass; 12 x 14 in.; autograph pencil short score, blue annotations, 12 staves (Box 56)
      Production no. 10700. Cue no. 14267. Record no. 1021.
    - Main Title, 6 pages; 12 x 14 in.; autograph pencil short score, red annotations, 12 staves (Box 56)
      Production no. 10700. Cue no. 14237. Record no. 1007.
    - Nickelodeon (cue title), 2 pages; fl,ob,cl,bsn,hn,tpt,tbn,perc,piano,strings; 12 x 14 in.; autograph pencil short score, red annotations, 12 staves (Box 56)
      Production no. 10700. Cue nos. 14255-56. Record no. 1015.
    - Pantomime (cue title), 6 pages; 12 x 14 in.; autograph pencil short score, red and blue annotations, 12 staves (Box 56)
      Production no. 10700. Cue no. 14253. Record no. 1014.
    - Sketch, 6 pages; 12 x 14 in.; autograph pencil sketch,blue annotations,12 staves (Box 56)
      Production no. 10700. Record no. 1005.
    - The Phone Call (cue title), 2 pages; fl,ob,cl,bsn,hn,tpt,per,harp,piano,strings; 12 x 14 in.; autograph pencil short score, red annotations, 12 staves (Box 56)
      Production no. 10700. Cue no. 14264. Record no. 1020.
    - Wear Make-Up (cue title), 2 pages; cl,bsn,perc,piano,strings; 12 x 14 in.; autograph pencil short score, red annotations, 12 staves (Box 56)
      Production no. 10700. Cue no. 14245. Record no. 1012.
  - An Old Fashioned Girl, Subseries 61.
    - Agreements, Budgets and Correspondence (Box 258)
  - Penelope, Subseries 63.
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 257)
    - Opera Script Masters (Box 257)
    - Public Relations Materials, 1971 (Box 257)
      Includes photo of Herschel Gilbert
    - Script and Tape Covers and Backs (Box 257)
    - Seattle Opera Association schedule, bills, etc., 1970-1971 (Box 257)
    - Synopsis (Box 257)
  - Perry Mason, Subseries 64.
    - Perry Mason, 1964 September 14; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 190)
      Tape Reel: 1118. Log or Cue# 1991-2021.
  - Peter and the Wolf, Subseries 130.
    - Text adapted by Gilbert (Box 278)
      Peter & the Wolf by Serge Prokofieff, Text freely adapted by Phil Sharp & H.B. Gilbert, page 1
  - Pinocchio, Subseries 65.
    - Correspondence, Musical Breakdown, 1949 (Box 260)
    - Pinochio, 1963 December 29; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 200)
      Tape reel: 1270.
  - Poor Albert and Little Annie, Subseries 67.
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 260)
  - Pop Goes the Weasel, Subseries 120.
    - Unidentified Material, 1947 (Box 260)
  - Project Moonbase, Subseries 68.
    - Financial Papers, 1953 (Box 260)
    - Project Moonbase, 1974 August; open reel audio tape (Box 192)
      Tape reel: 50. Television score.
    - Project Moonbase Conductor's Sketches and Cue Numbers, 1953 January (Box 65)
  - The Rifleman, Subseries 70.
    - Air Dates (Box 281)
    - Autograph Literary Notes, 1959 March 12; 23 pages; 8.5 x 11; 8.5 x 13 in.; autograph manuscript notes (Box 67)
      Record no. 106. Autograph pencil, pen notes, original and photocopy.
    - Autograph Literary Notes, 1959 March 12; 23 pages; 8.5 x 11; 8.5 x 13 in.; autograph manuscript notes (Box 68)
    - Autograph Literary Notes, 1959 March 12; 23 pages; 8.5 x 11; 8.5 x 13 in.; autograph manuscript notes (Box 69)
    - Autograph Sketch, 1 pages; piano sketch; 9.5 x 12 in. (Box 67)
      Found with Rifleman instrumental breakdown and other Rifleman notes.Record no. 104.
    - Autograph Sketch, 1 pages; piano sketch; 9.5 x 12 in. (Box 68)
      Found with Rifleman instrumental breakdown and other Rifleman notes. Record no. 104.
    - Autograph Sketch, 1 pages; piano sketch; 9.5 x 12 in. (Box 69)
    - Bills, Receipts, 1958 (Box 281)
      From Munich.
    - BMG correspondence re" Treasury of the West Vol 2 - The Rifleman and referenced clearance (Box 251)
    - Chuck Connors Photograph (Box 281)
      Promotional photograph.
    - Chuck Connors, Johnny Crawford Photographs (Box 281)
      Promotional photographs
    - Contracts and Agreements, 1992 (Box 251)
      Video Mechanical License Agreement between HB Gilbert/John Paul Music & Benson Music Group - The Rifleman
    - Correspondence from EMG (Box 281)
      re: clearance for The Rifleman Theme
    - Cue Sheets (Box 237)
    - Dubbing and Production Shooting Schedules, 1959 (Box 281)
    - End Credits, 1958 July 17; 5 pages; Fl,ob.,Eng.hn,2clBb,bsn,4hns,3 tpts, perc, 3 tbns, tuba, guitar piano, timp,violin,cello,bass; 11 x 17 in.; autograph/photocopy? full score, 18 stave, click marks in colored pencil (Box 67)
      Studio: Four Star. Cue no. RET- 101. Record no. 37. Black ink autograph/photocopy? music manuscript. In folder marked Four Star Music, Library Set 3, 100's.
    - End Credits, 1958 July 17; 5 pages; Fl,ob.,Eng.hn,2clBb,bsn,4hns,3 tpts, perc, 3 tbns, tuba, guitar piano, timp,violin,cello,bass; 11 x 17 in.; autograph/photocopy? full score, 18 stave, click marks in colored pencil (Box 68)
    - End Credits, 1958 July 17; 5 pages; Fl,ob.,Eng.hn,2clBb,bsn,4hns,3 tpts, perc, 3 tbns, tuba, guitar piano, timp,violin,cello,bass; 11 x 17 in.; autograph/photocopy? full score, 18 stave, click marks in colored pencil (Box 69)
    - Fan Letters to Gilbert (Box 288)
    - Fan Mail Requests, 1959-1961 (Box 270)
      fan mail and requests for song or music from the series
    - Financial Papers, 1963-1966 (Box 268)
    - Instrumental Breakdown, 1958 August 4; 1 pages; 9.5 x 13 in.; instrumental break-down of musical numbers form with ms additions (Box 67)
      Found with other Rifleman notes and literary manuscripts. Record no. 105.
    - Instrumental Breakdown, 1958 August 4; 1 pages; 9.5 x 13 in.; instrumental break-down of musical numbers form with ms additions (Box 68)
    - Instrumental Breakdown, 1958 August 4; 1 pages; 9.5 x 13 in.; instrumental break-down of musical numbers form with ms additions (Box 68)
    - Instrumental Breakdown, 1958 August 4; 1 pages; 9.5 x 13 in.; instrumental break-down of musical numbers form with ms additions (Box 69)
    - Letter from tambourine re: mechanical license for The Rifleman, unsigned agreement (Box 251)
    - Lively Lucas based on "Lively Lucas Theme", 1961 May 17; 19 pages; 2 fl, 2 ob, 2 cl, bsn, 3 hns, 3 tpt, 3 tbn,2 perc,timp,viol,cello,bass; 11 x 17 in.; photocopy autograph full score, 23 staves (Box 67)
      Cue no. 4811. Record no. 94.
    - Lively Lucas based on "Lively Lucas Theme", 1961 May 17; 19 pages; 2 fl, 2 ob, 2 cl, bsn, 3 hns, 3 tpt, 3 tbn,2 perc,timp,viol,cello,bass; 11 x 17 in.; photocopy autograph full score, 23 staves (Box 68)
    - Lively Lucas based on "Lively Lucas Theme", 1961 May 17; 19 pages; 2 fl, 2 ob, 2 cl, bsn, 3 hns, 3 tpt, 3 tbn,2 perc,timp,viol,cello,bass; 11 x 17 in.; photocopy autograph full score, 23 staves (Box 69)
    - Lou Mallory (cue title), 1962 September 30; 3 pages; 2 fl,ob,cl,basscl,contrabasscl,3 tbn,2perc,bass; 11 x 17 in; photocopy full score, red,orange,purple,blue, green annotations (Box 66)
      Cue no. 5212. Record no. 1086. 14000's RX recorded in Munich July-August '61. In a file marked Recorded Bridges RX. This cue found in Library set 3.
    - Lou Mallory (cue title), 1962 September 30; 3 pages; 2 fl,ob,cl,basscl,contrabasscl,3 tbn,2perc,bass; 11 x 17 in; photocopy full score, red,orange,purple,blue, green annotations (Box 67)
    - Lou Mallory (cue title), 1962 September 30; 3 pages; 2 fl,ob,cl,basscl,contrabasscl,3 tbn,2perc,bass; 11 x 17 in; photocopy full score, red,orange,purple,blue, green annotations (Box 68)
    - Lou Mallory (cue title), 1962 September 30; 3 pages; 2 fl,ob,cl,basscl,contrabasscl,3 tbn,2perc,bass; 11 x 17 in; photocopy full score, red,orange,purple,blue, green annotations (Box 69)
    - Lou Scared (cue title), 1962 October 2; 2 pages; 2fl,ob,cl,basscl,contrabasscl,tpt,3tbn,perc, bass; 11 x 17 in; photocopy full score, red,orange,blue,darkblue annotations (Box 66)